卡洛琳 我到家啦
Caroline, I'm home!
我是说 到酒店啦
I mean, I'm hotel!
我在楼上
I'm upstairs,
因为我们现在有楼上啦
because we have an upstairs!
谢谢你损失万贯家财
Thank you for losing all your money
现在好莱坞才会要买你的故事
so Hollywood would buy your story
我也才有机会大买特买大麻
and I could buy all the pot I want.
亲爱的 你好 你正好赶上
Hello, darling. You're just in time
看我隆重好莱坞登场
for my big Hollywood entrance.
稍等 垃圾女神
Hold up, Greta Garbage.
我想先跟厄尔说这里大麻的事儿
I just want to tell Earl about the pot sitch out here.
他一定觉得特嗨好笑
He'll think it's high-larious.
你每次都不想看人家走路
You never want to watch me walk.
厄尔 干嘛呢 是你的宝贝麦克斯
What up, Earl? It's your girl, Max,
从加州大 麻莱坞给你致电
calling from Holly-weed, Cali-juana.
麦克斯 你不在 这里都不一样了
Hey, Max, it's not the same without you here.
少了好多客人被弄哭
A lot less customers crying.
听我说
Listen to this!
这里随便就发给你医用大麻许可卡
They just give you pot cards out here.
我跟医生说"宝宝有时会不开心"就拿到了
All I had to say was "Sure, I get sad."
我这样在没出路的餐厅工作的80岁老人
Hey, I'm an 80-year-old man working at a dead-end diner.
我赌我这理由能拿两张卡
I bet I'd get two cards.
是麦克斯吗 让我跟她说
Is that Max? Let me talk to her.
我的白色高球手套肯定是被你偷拿走了
I can't find my white golf glove, and I know you took it!
阿憨 别看到黑影就开枪
Han, keep your panties on.
我不知道你的手套上哪去了
I have no idea where your glove is.
开车这段信号不好
Oh, I'm driving through the hills.
这里...信号...不好
I'm...breaking...up.
好了 本姑娘的隆重好莱坞登场
Okay, here comes my big Hollywood entrance.
亲爱的你好 希望没让你等太久
Hello, darling--I hope I haven't kept you waiting.
天啊 你没事吧
Oh, my God! Are you okay?
我对好莱坞的爱 让我人仰马翻
I'm head over heels for Hollywood, baby.
你就把食物放在通常
Just put it wherever you would usually put things
与好莱坞编剧的隆重会议 写你人生故事时
for, like, a big Hollywood meeting with screenwriters
会放的位置就行
who are writing your life story.
吧台呗
So, the counter?
跟着你的直觉走
Go with your instincts.
如果我要跟着直觉走
If I'd gone with my instincts,
那我当时就会念完护士学位
I would've finished nursing college.
我爱洛城的另一个原因呢
Another reason I love LA?
就是我们吃早午餐的餐厅 居然有代客停狗
We just had brunch at a place where you can valet park your dog.
天啊 麦克斯 那是新墨镜吗
Oh, my God, Max, are those new sunglasses?
兰迪买给我的
Randy got them for me.
没办法 你的那副墨镜没散架
I had to. Your other pair of sunglasses
全凭它自身的意志力
were being held together by willpower,
与一块四周大的口香糖
and four-week-old gum.
今晚有空共进晚餐吗
Can you have dinner tonight?
吃晚餐是不是就代表又得跟你滚床单
Ah, would that mean I have to have sex with you again?
因为我的答案是 好的
Because the answer is yes.
麦克斯 你又要跟兰迪去约会啊
Max, you're going out with Randy again?
我们到了这里之后 你就整天不见蛋
I've barely seen you since we got here.
反而大卫·史威默我都碰见他四次了
And I've seen David Schwimmer four times.
我还没见过他呢
I've never met David Schwimmer,
这倒是挺奇怪 因为我蛮确定我是他律师
which is weird 'cause I'm pretty sure I'm his lawyer.
你何不跟我们一起吃饭呢
Why don't you come to dinner with us?
这是否代表她又得跟你滚床单
Would that mean she has to have sex with you again?
因为我的答案是 好的
Because that's a yes!
其实我现在这么一想
Actually, now I think of it,
我可以介绍你跟我一个老朋友认识
I can set you up with an old friend of mine.
他在这里可是知名大人物
He is big in this town.
有三明治以他为名这么出名
Deli-sandwich- named-after-him big.
如果你跟大牌三明治好上
If you start dating a big sandwich,
我会很嫉妒呢
I'm gonna be really jealous.
今晚见
See you later?
请盯着我的巨乳好吗
My boobs are down here.
穿可爱点
Wear something cute.
好吧
Okay.
上一次有男人让你穿可爱点
Last time a guy told you to wear something cute,
你回答"啥可爱 你的蛋蛋吗"
You said, "Like what? Yo nuts?"
你真的很喜欢这男的啊
You really like this guy.
你能别再一直说出
Oh, can you just not ruin this for me
到底好在哪了吗 都没惊喜了
by pointing out what's good about it?
-零食 -别吃
- Ooh, snacks. - No, don't eat those.
这是为跟编剧开会准备的
That's for the meeting with the writers.
编剧就是弃疗的演员 所以他们可以随便吃
Writers are actors who gave up, so they're allowed to eat.
我们能聊聊选谁来演吗
Can we talk about casting with these writers?
这次我想要个有知名度的人演我
Because for once, I want a name to play me,
而不是只是别的节目里的杂鱼临演
not just some lady who falls out of her tube top on "Cops."
大家安安
Hi, everybody!
苏菲 我还以为这时间你是去找那个名医
Sophie, I thought you were gonna be at the healer
来帮你怀孕
who's gonna help you get pregnant
所以要让会议结束很久之后才回来
until well after our meeting.
你错了
Well, you're wrong.
那位名医取消了我的预约
My healer had to cancel.
她得先去帮金·卡戴珊再次怀孕
She's trying to get Kim Kardashian pregnant again.
是她还是侃爷怀啊
Or is it Kanye?
我忘了他俩谁才是女人
I forget which one's the girl.
我挺确定是侃爷
I'm pretty sure it's Kanye,
因为他每个月都会在网上发疯乱讲话一次
because he's the one that goes crazy once a month.
好兴奋啊 我们的电影会议要开始了
This is so exciting. Our movie meeting is happening!
的确很兴奋
This is exciting.
这是我首次不是因为
I've never been in a hotel meeting
贴"小广告"而跟人在酒店见面
that didn't start on Craigslist.
-你好 -你好 我叫莱斯丽
- Hi! - Hi, I'm Leslie.
他是杰森 他是我搭档[伴侣]
This is Jason. He's my partner.
编剧搭档
Writing partner.
先解释清楚 我只跟模特约会
To be clear, I only date models.
先解释清楚 是手模
Hand models, to be clear.
请进
Come on in.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing.
估计你在谷歌搜图上见过我
You probably recognize me from Google Images.
我拿着被剪掉的信用卡
The photo of me being dragged out of Barneys crying
哭着被高档百货的人拖出来的照片太经典
with my cut up credit cards is classic.
我叫麦克斯·布莱克 如果你谷歌搜我图
And I'm Max Black. If you Google Image me,
你就会看到被我盗窃身份的加拿大男子
you'll see the Canadian dude I stole my identity from.
你好性感 你是模特吗
You're hot. Are you a model?
这样太不专业了
That is so unprofessional.
说得好像我才是被法院限制
Right. Like I'm the one who has to stay
不许接近佛莱德·萨维奇的人
500 feet away from Fred Savage.
他真的太可爱了
He's just so darn cute!
总之 你好
Anyway, hi.
你好 好的 我们换个话题
Hi, okay, yeah. Let's switch focus
坐下来聊聊电影吧
and sit and talk movie.
我已经想到了我角色的口头禅
I already came up with my character's catch phrase.
我觉得每次我的角色要离场时 就说
I think every time I leave the room, I should say
"我个我个去"
"Jigga jigga damn."
我们以为只会是我们跟卡洛琳之间谈
We thought it was just gonna be us and Caroline,
不是嫌弃你不好玩 或是不美
not that you're not fun and fabulous.
你就像清醒版的梅根·福克斯[女星]
You're like a sober Megan Fox.
我迷糊了 我以为你会想跟
I'm confused. I assumed you wanted to meet
我们两个人一起见面
with both of us because, you know,
毕竟麦克斯在故事中的地位举足轻重
Max is a huge part of the story.
别发短信了 帮帮我
Stop texting. Help me.
这只是一场无聊的初步认识会议
This is just a boring, preliminary, get-to-know-you meeting.
-所以最好就是... -我不在
- It would really be better if-- - I wasn't here.
别人不想要我时 我感觉得到
Yeah, I get it. I know when I'm not wanted.
所以我尽早逃出我妈的子宫了
That's why I high-tailed it out of my mother's womb.
反正 我自己也有一场隆重的好莱坞会议
Anyway, I have a big Hollywood meeting myself.
-是吗 -对啊
- You do? - Uh, yeah.
我有一个预约 我得去排队
I have an appointment to go stand in line
报名一个节目叫《价格竞猜》
for a little thing called "The Price Is Right."
你们听过吗
You ever heard of it?
这么出名你们铁定听过
Ah, you know you have.
麦克斯 你不用走
Max, you don't have to go.
没事 没事的
It's cool, it's cool.
说到这里 我想说
And with that, let me just say,
我个我个去
jigga jigga damn.
事情是这样的
So, here's the thing.
电影里没有你朋友这个角色
Your friend's character is not in the movie.
我们可以不用说那句"我个我个去"啊
We don't have to do that "Jigga jigga damn" thing.
我说实话 我从没听她说过这个
To be honest, I've never heard her say that.
跟你的朋友无关
Nothing personal to your friend.
-她很正点 -知道你迷她
- She's hot. - We get it!
但当红女星詹妮弗·劳伦斯想出演你
But Jennifer Lawrence is interested in playing you.
她想演出个勇敢素颜的角色
And she wants to do a brave, no-makeup role.
还得是唯一女主角
Without a co-star.
詹妮弗·劳伦斯想演我吗
Jennifer Lawrence wants to play me?
我个我个去
Jigga jigga damn!
你今晚想再次留宿我家吗
So you want to sleep over again tonight?
你妈妈会答应吗
Think your mom will let you?
大概会吧 我五岁她就让我工作了
Maybe. She let me get a job at five.
你们俩坐在餐桌同一边吗
You guys are sitting on the same side of the table?
麦克斯 你曾因此把人踢出过餐厅呢
Max, you've kicked people out of the diner for that!
而且人家是奶奶跟孙子
And it was a boy and his nana.
我以前在晚饭时也坐过别人旁边啊
I've sat next to people before at dinner.
流浪汉之家的人半强迫大家排排坐
They kind of make you at the shelter.
来点干白吗
Some wine?
非廉价盒装的干白吗
Wine that's not from a box?
当然好啦
That's a yes!
对了《价格竞猜》怎么样了
Anyway, how was "The Price Is Right"?
你见到那个主持人了吗 我想他是叫...
Did you get to meet the host, I want to say
艾利克斯·沙杰克
Alex Sajack?
忍住怒火 麦克斯
Control that temper, Max.
是德鲁·凯利 他可是一周有五天
It's Drew Carey, and he gets housewives wet
都能让主妇下面湿哒哒的男人 记好了
five days a week-- know the facts.
但我今天太晚到了 只能明天再去排
But I showed up too late, so I got to go back tomorrow.
我在想 明天穿的T恤上面写着
I was thinking of wearing a shirt that said
"竞猜猪一样 手气屎一样"
"One in the Plinko, two in the stinko."
我直接买一辈子分量的便餐包给你吧
How about I buy you a lifetime supply of Rice-A-Roni?
你大概没意识到我吃的量能把你吃破产
I don't think you realize how much Rice-A-Roni I can eat.
鲍伯来了
Oh, there's Bob.
鲍伯 我们在这边
Bob! We're over here.
你好啊 帅哥
Oh, hey there, hot shot.
这是你要撮合的鲍伯 还是同名朋友
Is that my date Bob, or a different Bob?
请告诉我他只是刚好同名
I need that to be a different Bob.
我觉得他是史上第一个鲍伯
I think that's the very first Bob.
当年就是亚当 夏娃与鲍伯三人
It was Adam, Eve, and Bob.
卡洛琳 这位是鲍伯
Caroline, this is Bob.
鲍伯 这位是卡洛琳·钱宁
Bob, meet Caroline Channing.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
上面不太有料啊
Not a lot on top.
希望"上面"是指我的脑子没料
I hope he means I'm stupid.
如果我跟兰迪算是老少配
If me and Randy are May-December,
那你们就是穿越恋啊
you two are May-Dead.
马龙·白兰度在《教父》中演得赞到不行
Marlon Brando played the pants off the Godfather.
这事毋庸置疑
You bet your ass he did.
但说到底 他还不是亲我戒指[臣服于我]
At the end of the day, he was kissing my ring.
说到亲 我上一次接吻
Speaking of kissing, I haven't gotten one
还是鲍伯跟老牌滚石乐队一起吸毒的时候呢
since that time Bob did heroin with the Stones.
你是说他们来跟着我吸毒的那会吧
I think you mean the time the Stones did heroin with Bob.
有"想法"了吗
Getting any ideas?
有啊 我想60岁前就死去
Yeah, that I want to die before 60.
有人想"来一发"吗
Anybody want to do a little blow?
我就算了
I'm gonna pass.
我们得小心啊 鲍伯
We have to be careful, Bob.
我们的生命力没你坚强啊
Some of us are capable of dying.
我也算了
I'm gonna pass as well.
我不吸粉
I don't do snorties.
话痨的我 都怕有些人吸完滔滔不绝的程度
Even I'm scared of how much talking there'd be.
呜 呜 火车要离站啦
Toot, toot. The train is leaving.
兰迪
Um, Randy?
谢谢你很好心给我撮合对象
It was really nice of you to set me up,
但你想啥呢
but what the hell were you thinking?
我跟他起码差了100岁吧
There's a 100-year age difference!
卡洛琳 这里是好莱坞
Caroline, this is Hollywood.
年龄不是问题
Age doesn't matter.
除非你是女人
Unless you're a woman.
再说了 鲍伯人脉广
Plus, Bob's got a lot of connections.
你的事他真能提供很多帮助呢
He could really help you with your deal.
我才不要跟上帝当年的大学舍友"睡"
I'm not gonna sleep with God's college roommate
好换取在好莱坞能出头
to get ahead in Hollywood.
我觉得跟这老人 睡就好 不需要"睡"
I think sleeping's pretty much all you'd have to do.
没"吸"到
Never got to the blow.
撞到我第四任前妻
Ran into my fourth ex-wife,
只是这一次不是
only this time it wasn't with
用我路虎前的防撞杆"撞"
the moose bumper on my Range Rover.
你这年纪还在开车啊
You're still driving?
你们俩美女来好莱坞干嘛
What are you dolls doing in Hollywood?
你俩是走姐妹花之类的路线吗
You girls like a sister act or something?
算吧 有人要拍一部关于我们的电影
Kind of. They're making a movie about us,
对了 那俩编剧怎么说
So, what did the writers say?
他们觉得扎克·加利费安纳基斯演我怎么样
What did they think about Zach Galifianakis playing me?
不是针对你个人
Well, it's nothing personal,
但那俩编剧不想让你...
but the writers don't feel like you're...
这电影里的故事太多了
It's just, there's so much story.
而且角色也已经有很多了
There's a lot of characters already.
你出局了 孩子
You're out of the picture, kid.
真的吗 我出局了吗
Really? I'm out?
麦克斯 很抱歉 我跟他们说了你至关重要
Max, I'm sorry. I told them you are crucial.
但当他们说没准詹妮弗·劳伦斯会来演我时
But then they said maybe Jennifer Lawrence would play me
我有点两眼发黑 心也跟着变黑了
and I kind of blacked out after that.
我被踢出过很多人生故事
Hey, I've been cut out of a lot of life stories,
比如我妈每次遇见一个新男人
like my mom's, every time she met a guy.
我就变成她的两岁清洁小女工
I was just her two-year-old cleaning lady.
麦克斯 好莱坞就是这样
Max, this is just the way Hollywood works.
鲍伯 你就知道好莱坞是如此
Bob, you know how Hollywood is.
你见证了它的成长
You were there when it started.
没事没事 兰迪 你准备好了吗
It's cool, it's cool. Randy, you ready?
是的 我们要在下一个故事前离开 鲍伯
Yeah, we're gonna take off before the next story, Bob.
我已经听了很多次
I can only hear about that three-way
你和加文·麦格诺3P的风流韵事了
with Gavin MacLeod so many times.
再说了 我得早起
Plus, I have to get up early
排队去参加《价格竞猜》
to get in line for "The Price Is Right."
我以前还照看过小鲍比·巴克呢
I used to babysit little Bobby Barker.
麦克斯 别走 留下来再喝一杯
Max, don't leave. Stay for another drink.
不了 我出局了
Nah, I'm out.
我吸可卡因的刀片借你
Wow, you could cut that tension
一刀切断这紧绷的气氛
with my coke blade.
麦克斯很坚强 我们是一个团队
Max is tough. We're a team.
我们一起经历了很多
We've been through a lot together,
一起经受家里花洒坏了 去洗车机洗澡的事
including a car wash that time our shower broke.
你会没事的 孩子
You'll be fine, kid.
等你电影上映了
You're gonna have plenty of friends
你会收获很多朋友
when your movie comes out,
交情能维持半年呢
and for six months after that.
我不需要虚伪的朋友 我有麦克斯
I don't need fake friends. I have Max.
韦斯利·斯奈普斯当年也是这么说简·方达
That's what Wesley Snipes said about Jane Fonda.
他们不是朋友啊
They're not friends.
你说得太对了
You bet your ass they're not.
我以为你不会有时间
I thought you weren't gonna have time
来上《价格竞猜》
to be on "The Price Is Right,"
你得上卡洛琳那部...
with Caroline's big
我觉得吧 肯定是无聊的大片
and I'm assuming boring movie.
我超有空
Well, my schedule's wide open.
当涉及到电影时 我退出[拔出]
When it comes to the movie, I pulled out.
我经常告诉男人我会这么做
You know, like I always tell guys I'm going to.
是奥列格
Oh, it's Oleg.
我猜他肯定想跟我电话爱爱
I bet you he wants to have phone sex.
有什么东西可以让我靠着吗
Is there anything I can lean on?
苏菲
Hey, Sophie.
我刚才在做嫩肋排
I was just making some baby back ribs
于是我想 我要我的嫩妹屁屁
and I thought, I want my baby back
然后我用烤箱手套撸了一发
Then I pleasured myself with an oven mitt.
所以不爱爱吗
So, no sex?
我看见这有一张长椅 高度正好
'Cause I see a bench. It's a perfect height,
而且我可以让麦克斯帮咱俩拿着手机
and I can have Max hold the phone for us.
是苏菲吗 她是不是跟麦克斯一起
Is that Sophie? Is she with Max?
电话给我
Give me that.
阿憨找你
It's Han,
距离越远 他听起来越矮
and you know sounds even shorter long-distance.
麦克斯 你是不是乱改我的手机铃声了
Max, did you play with the ringtone on my phone?
每次我手机响 就会发出叫床声
Every time it rings, it makes sex sounds.
母亲大人
Mother.
我等会再打给你
I have to call you back.
听起来她自己也过得挺爽嘛
Sounds like she's doing just fine on her own.
我要怎么弄掉这叫床声
How do I make the sex sounds stop?
对你而言 这难得一遇啊
For you, it's a rare occurrence.
就把手机放裤兜里 好好享受吧
Just leave it in your pants and enjoy it.
麦克斯
So, Max--
抱歉 阿憨 我听不清
Sorry, Han. I can't hear you.
开车这段信号不好
I'm driving through the hills.
这里...信号...不好
I'm...breaking...up aah...ahh...
我"来"了 母亲大人
I'm coming, Mother!
挑选选手的人来了
Ooh, here comes the contestant picker.
快假装你是中西部的全职妈妈
Act like you're a stay-at-home mom from the Midwest.
那是这节目的最佳入选条件
That's the "Price Is Right" sweet spot.
好的 你看这样行吗
Okay, how's this?
老天
Oh, God.
那些小混蛋让我忙得精疲力尽
Those little bastards are just running me ragged.
-选我 -选我
- Pick me! - Pick me!
我们有很多12岁的小男孩假装生病了
We got a lot of 12-year-old boys playing sick at home.
你们俩能这样上蹦下跳多久
How long can you ladies jump up and down for?
20分钟
20 minutes.
请出列
Step out of line.
这身是什么衣服
What is that costume?
花花绿绿全职妈妈装
Oh, this is home-bedazzled, doncha know?
请出列
Step out of line.
真高兴我终于走出家门了
I'm just glad to be out of the house.
在这里等着 你们俩入选了
Wait here. You're both in the mix.
先练习一下见到德鲁·凯里兴奋不已的样子
Practice being excited to meet Drew Carey.
他一眼就能识破你们是不是假兴奋
He knows when you're faking it.
我的鲍伯从未识破我是不是假"性奋"
My Bob never knows when I'm faking it.
保持下去 我喜欢你的热辣活力
Keep it up. I like your pepper.
麦克斯 我到处找你
Max! I've been looking all over for you.
你来这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
这里可不是电影里的场景
This isn't a scene in the movie.
我知道 因为这里有我
I know, because I'm in it.
麦克斯 没有你就不会有这部电影
Max, there would be no movie without you.
没有我 家乡自助餐厅也不会有武装警卫啊
There would also be no armed guards at HomeTown Buffet.
你想说什么
What's your point?
我本能早点来这里
I would've been here sooner,
但我刚跟鲍伯从赌城回来
but I just got back from Vegas with Bob.
他输掉了5万美元
He lost $50,000,
还有菲·唐纳薇的奥斯卡
and somehow Faye Dunaway's Oscar.
我和鲍伯在直升飞机上聊了很多关于友情的事
But Bob and I talked a lot about friendship on the helicopter.
就在我用肾上腺素注射器
You know, right after I jump-started his heart
让他的心脏重新起跳后
with the epi pen.
我和你决不会变成
And you and I are not gonna be
薇诺娜·瑞德和格温妮丝·帕特洛
Winona Ryder and Gwyneth Paltrow.
或是苏菲和格温妮丝·帕特洛
Or Sophie and Gwyneth Paltrow!
那个贱人
That bitch.
我本来想给我第一个孩子起名为"小苹果"
I was going to name my first-born "Apple,"
没想到被她抢了
and she took it.
现在只能勉强起名为"小油饼"
Now I have to settle for "Fritter."
我不会为了钱而牺牲我们的友情
I am not gonna sell out our friendship for Hollywood.
麦克斯 电影必须有你 你现在跟我
Max, you're in the movie and you're coming with me
去会上告诉他们这点
to the meeting to tell them that.
但我入选了
But I'm in the mix.
他们真心要我留在这里
They actually want me here.
但我也要你去那里陪我
But I want you there.
你应该和我这个蠢货在一起
I'm the stupid you should be with.
好吧 不管了
All right, screw it.
苏菲 我要跟她走
Sophie, I'm gonna go with her.
做过这么多坏决定 也不差这一个
Why stop making bad decisions now?
好吧 但我得在队伍里再交一个朋友
All right, but I'm gonna have to make another friend in line.
你好 我是芭布
Hi, I'm Barb.
老天 拼车和花生奶油三明治真是...
Oh, gosh, carpool and fluffernutter...
都怪小孩要踢足球 对吧
because soccer, right?
麦克斯 这算是我们第一场好莱坞派对
Max, this is kind of our first Hollywood party.
我知道 我很好奇我会跟谁回家
I know. I wonder who I'll go home with.
估计又是安德鲁·戴斯·克雷吧
Probably Andrew Dice Clay again.
听着 这可能是
Hey listen, this might be
第六杯小小龙舌兰酒的胡话
the sixth teeny, tiny, tequila talking,
但谢谢你站出来维护我
but thanks for standing up for me
没有让那些编剧把我从你的人生中踢出去
and not letting those writers cut me out of your life.
麦克斯 这番话意义非凡
Oh, Max, that means a lot.
我喜欢你喝醉时友好的样子
I love it when you're drunk and nice.
不好 是阿憨
Oh, no, it's Han.
好奇他打来干嘛
Wonder what he wants.
你觉得他是不是终于发现
You think he finally realized
我把餐厅答录机的录音改成
I changed the outgoing message on the diner
"欢迎致电拉稀小镇"
to "Welcome to Diarrhea-ville?"
麦克斯 我听到答录机的录音了
Max, I heard the outgoing message,
我还发现我办公室有一系列《小鬼当家》风的陷阱
and I found a series of Home Alone-style traps in my office,
一个比一个更邪恶更妙
each one more fiendishly clever than the last.
我不知道你怎么把那些山羊弄进他办公室
And I don't know how you got those goats in his office,
但我们现在很难把它们弄出去
but we're having a hard time getting them out.
下一招是啥 麦克斯
What's next, Max?
是什么会让我最终折服[下跪]
What will finally bring me to my knees?
不知道 一个长得像女孩的男孩吗
I don't know. A guy who kind of looks like a girl?
为什么你要对我百般折磨
Why are you doing all of this to me?
我只是不希望我不在的时候 你忘了我
I just didn't want you to forget me while I was away.
麦克斯
Oh, Max.
你说得我都要落泪了
Now you've brought me to tears.
恭喜 麦克斯
Congratulations, Max.
你终于惹他生气[给他羊]了
You finally got his goat.
快来人救我
Somebody help me!
保护好蛋蛋
Cover those nuts.
说不定某天传宗接代时会需要
You may need them one day.
我喜欢你是个东西海岸恶霸
I like that you're a bi-coastal bully.
我们第二部可以拍这个
That might be our sequel.
我忘了告诉你
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
我邀请了两位男士过来
I invited a couple of guys over.
谁 我现在可是名花有主的
Who? I'm kind of seeing someone-ish.
是兰迪和鲍伯啦
It's Randy and Bob.
鲍伯是真实存在的吗
Bob was real?
我以为他是个老鬼呢
I thought he was a ghost.
姑娘们 我带了香槟
Hey, girls. I brought some bubbly
来庆祝你们今天的胜利
to celebrate your victory today,
鲍伯带了多种多样的鸦片和兴奋剂
and Bob brought a wide variety of opiates and stimulants.
我很高兴看到你俩为友情坚持到底
Oh, I'm glad to see you two stuck it out.
真正的友谊犹如凤毛麟角
True friendship is a rare thing.
这世上我只相信过一个人
There's only one man I've ever trusted,
就是安杰丽卡·休斯顿
and that is Anjelica Huston.
哇靠
Holy crap!
是上帝来接鲍伯了吧
I think God is here for Bob.
这直升机是来接你的吗
Is that chopper for you?
你说得太对了
You bet your ass it is.
我要去马里布
I'm going to Malibu.
苏珊·萨兰登叫了披萨
Susan Sarandon is ordering pizza.
我们要嗑摇头丸
We're doing molly.
鲍伯
Bob.
我们还会见面吗
Will I ever see you again?
别着急 小猫咪 我才刚出来
Slow down, pussycat. I'm just getting out of something.
那男人的确非常了解该如何退场
That man sure knows how to make an exit.
不是退出生命 而是退出其他事情
Not from life, but from everything else.
我得走了 宝贝
I gotta go, doll.
鲍伯会顺道送我回家
Bob's gonna drop me off at home.
希望这次我能降落在泳池里
Hopefully, I'll land in my pool this time.
我不知道是什么原因 但是...
I don't know what it is, but
鲍伯令我疯狂
I'm crazy about Bob.
我懂 妹子
Get it, girl.